Bhagyashree Walanj

Helmholtzstraße, 21, Berlin Germany- 10587

Software Developer

shree.6490@gmail.com

DOB: 6th April, 1990 Gender: Female Status: Married

Skills

A Skilled front-end developer with strong experience in enhancing User Experience by designing and developing solutions that blend seamless experience with operational efficiency for users.

Technical expertise of more than 5+ years includes **React JS**, **React-Redux**, **HTML**, **Bootstrap**, **JavaScript**, **ES6**, **Responsive Design UI**, **Visual Studio**

Currently looking for the post of Frontend developer in germany

Experience

Autoplant Systems/ Senior Software Developer

August 2020 - Feb 2021, Navi Mumbai

AutoTAT Project:

Responsibilities:

- Implemented various screens for the front end using React.js and used various predefined components from NPM (Node Package Manager) and redux library.
- Experience in **RESTful web services** integrated by **React-Redux**.
- Experience with handling manual Forms implementation using ReactJS By React-Redux form array Library.
- Implemented MapMyIndia maps on ReactJS components.
- Implemented React container and presentational components (as Stateless and Functional components when applicable).

Technologies Used: ReactJS Libraries, Github, sourceTree, Material-UI, React-Bootstrap, React-Redux, ReactRedux Form Array, MapMyIndia Plugins, ES6 Javascript, Typescript

Novire Technologies Pvt Ltd/ Senior Software Developer

Sept 2014 - August 2021, Navi Mumbai

IVTS Framework:

- Responsibilities:
- Implementation and delivery of Integrated Vehicle Tracking System (I.V.T.S) Project requirements.

- Handling inbound and outbound integration, both **Restful and SOAP services.**
- Worked on the MapMyIndia plugin and rest APIs.
- Worked on Implementation of tableau services on UI with JavaScript
- **Business Logic** Jobs for automated report generation and send data to clients.
- Helps to track orders in transit, provide route optimization reports, and monitor vehicles inside yards and plants, so that customers can meet delivery compliance and improve logistics.
- Agile Process Management (Scrum Master).
- Leads Sprint Planning meetings.
- Identifying tasks that could be improved through automation.
- Hands on **Customized Module** Development.
- **Code review** and Code Testing on QC environment before the Production.
- Resolving **technical issues** faced by other team members.

Technologies Used: Javascript, HTML5, SVN, JQuery Plugins, Active MQ, Bootstrap 4, Datatables, JSON, XML

Education	
	UMIT College, SNDT University/ B.Tech (IT) 2007 -2011, Mumbai
	New English High School / 12th SCIENCE 2005 - 2007, Mumbai
	Sahakar Vidya Prasarak Mandal, School / 10th STD 2005, Mumbai
Languages	English, Hindi, Punjabi, Marathi
Hobbies	Exploring New technologies, Places and Food, Listening Music

Declaration: I hereby declare that the above details are true and to the best of my knowledge.

Bhagyashree Walanj